A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 6 FA1326
Rockefeller Archive Center
John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 6
1969-2014
Rockefeller Archive Center
John A. Hartford Foundation
FA1326
23.68 Cubic Feet 59 document boxes, 1 card file box
Scope and Contents Note
This series contains grant files from 1996 to 2014, plus a single grant from 1980 to 1985. It also contains a box of index cards that summarize the grants awarded from 1969 to 1977, first by grantee and then by project area.
Additionally, Boxes 514 to 516 contain a handful of files from 1996 for grant proposals designated with a standard grant number. However, those proposals were declined and labeled by the Foundation as "closed." To avoid confusion with the archival use of that term (referring to restricted content), each file is relabeled "declined." Box 516 also contains two proposals that were later withdrawn by the prospective grantees. Lastly, there are seven boxes with files on Foundation-assisted programs (FAP).
Bigraphical/Historical Note
The John A. Hartford Foundation (JAHF) was established in 1929 by brothers John and George Hartford, sons of the founder of the Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company (A&P). The foundation is a private, nonpartisan philanthropy dedicated to improving the care of older adults. For its first several decades, the foundation broadly supported clinical medical research. By 1982, it began to focus solely on geriatric healthcare. In 2015, JAHF paid out $20.2 million on a total of 80 active grants and committed $25.3 million to 24 new grants projects, all focused on the care of older adults.
Immediate Source of Acquisition Note
The John A. Hartford Foundation records were donated to RAC by JAHF in 2014. Record transfers to RAC began in 2014 and continue as needed.
Arrangement Note
Arranged as received
Conditions Governing Access Note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Other Finding Aids Note
For Series 1 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA771/collection
For Series 2 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1137/collection
For Series 3 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1218/collection
For Series 4 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1296/collection
For Series 5 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1297/collection
For Series 7 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1138/collection
- Grants, 6
  - Oregon Health and Science University: P. Archbold (2000-0097), 2000-2007 (Box 465, Folder 3450-3455)
  - Oregon Health and Science University: P. Archbold (2000-0097), 2000-2007 (Box 466, Folder 3456)
  - Oregon Health and Science University: H. Young (2005-0100), 2005-2011 (Box 466, Folder 3457-3461)
  - Oregon Health and Science University: T. Harvath (2010-0187), 2010-2013 (Box 467, Folder 3462-3464)
  - Stanford University: G. Stratos (2001-0466), 2001-2006 (Box 467, Folder 3465-3466)
  - University of Alabama at Birmingham: R. Allman (2000-0439), 2000-2006 (Box 467, Folder 3467)
  - University of Alabama at Birmingham: R. Allman (2004-0214), 2004-2009 (Box 468, Folder 3468)
  - University of Alabama at Birmingham: R. Allman (2008-0143), 2008-2011 (Box 468, Folder 3469)
  - Emory University: J. Ouslander (2000-0440), 2000-2005 (Box 468, Folder 3470)
  - Emory University: J. Ouslander (2004-0213), 2004-2009 (Box 468, Folder 3471)
  - Emory University: T. Johnson (2008-0142), 2008-2011 (Box 468, Folder 3472)
  - Society of Hospital Medicine: L. Wellikson (2004-0233), 2004-2007 (Box 469, Folder 3473-3477)
  - Society of Hospital Medicine: L. Wellikson (2006-0229), 2006-2011 (Box 469, Folder 3478)
  - Society of Hospital Medicine: L. Wellikson (2006-0229), 2006-2011 (Box 470, Folder 3479-3482)
  - Society of General Internal Medicine: D. Karlson (2002-0013), 2002-2006 (Box 470, Folder 3483-3484)
  - Society of General Internal Medicine: D. Karlson (2002-0013), 2002-2006 (Box 471, Folder 3485-3490)
  - Society of General Internal Medicine: D. Karlson (2002-0013), 2002-2006 (Box 472, Folder 3491)
  - Society of General Internal Medicine: C. Landefeld (2004-0154), 2004-2006 (Box 472, Folder 3492-3493)
  - Society of General Internal Medicine: D. Karlson (2005-0105), 2005-2006 (Box 472, Folder 3494)
  - Rush University Medical Center: S. Rothschild (2000-0312), 2000-2006 (Box 472, Folder 3495-3497)
  - Rush University Medical Center: S. Rothschild (2000-0312), 2000-2006 (Box 473, Folder 3498)
  - Rhode Island Hospital: R. Besdine (2007-0097), 2007-20011 (Box 473, Folder 3499)
  - University of California, San Diego: D. Jeste (2004-0338), 2004-2009 (Box 473, Folder 3500)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: D. Reuben (2002-0270), 2002-2007 (Box 473, Folder 3501)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: D. Reuben (2005-0060), 2005-2009 (Box 473, Folder 3502)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: D. Reuben (2006-0079), 2006-2011 (Box 474, Folder 3503)
  - University of Arkansas: C. Beverly (2000-0093), 2000-2006 (Box 474, Folder 3504-3508)
  - University of Arkansas: C. Beverly (2000-0093), 2000-2006 (Box 475, Folder 3509-3514)
  - University of Arkansas: C. Beverly (2000-0093), 2000-2006 (Box 476, Folder 3515)
  - University of Arkansas: C. Beverly (2005-0098), 2005-2011 (Box 476, Folder 3516-3519)
  - University of Arkansas: C. Beverly (2010-0188), 2010-2014 (Box 477, Folder 3520-3521)
  - University at Albany: A. Fortune (99-722), 1999-2002 (Box 477, Folder 3522-3526)
  - Research Foundation of State University of New York (SUNY): P. McCallion (2003-0210), 2003-2009 (Box 478, Folder 3527-3532)
  - Research Foundation of State University of New York (SUNY): V. Rizzo (2003-0210), 2003-2009 (Box 479, Folder 3533-3538)
  - Research Foundation of State University of New York (SUNY): V. Rizzo (2003-0210), 2003-2009 (Box 480, Folder 3539)
  - University of Hawaii: P. Blanchette (2004-0211), 2004-2008 (Box 480, Folder 3540)
  - University of Hawaii: P. Blanchette (2007-0006), 2007-2011 (Box 480, Folder 3541)
  - University of Colorado: A. Kramer (2003-0204), 2003-2007 (Box 480, Folder 3542)
  - University of Colorado: E. Coleman (2005-0194), 2005-2009 (Box 480, Folder 3543-3544)
  - University of Colorado: E. Coleman (2005-0194), 2005-2009 (Box 481, Folder 3545)
  - University of Colorado: R. Schwartz (2006-0169), 2006-2011 (Box 481, Folder 3546)
  - University of Colorado: E. Coleman (2007-0069), 2007-2012 (Box 481, Folder 3547-3550)
  - University of Colorado: E. Coleman (2008-0147), 2008-2013 (Box 482, Folder 3551-3553)
  - University of Chicago: G. Sachs (2003-0201), 2003-2008 (Box 482, Folder 3554)
  - University of Chicago: G. Sachs (2006-0168), 2006-2011 (Box 482, Folder 3555)
  - University of California, San Francisco: C. Landefeld (2003-0244), 2003-2007 (Box 482, Folder 3556)
  - University of California, San Francisco: M. Wallhagen (2005-0102), 2005-2011 (Box 483, Folder 3557-3562)
  - University of California, San Francisco: M. Wallhagen (2005-0102), 2005-2011 (Box 484, Folder 3563)
  - University of California, San Francisco: C. Johnston (2005-0061), 2005-2008 (Box 484, Folder 3564-3566)
  - University of California, San Francisco: C. Landefeld (2006-0108), 2006-2011 (Box 484, Folder 3567-3568)
  - University of California, San Francisco: M. Wallhagen (2010-0189), 2010-2013 (Box 484, Folder 3569-3570)
  - University of California, San Diego: D. Jeste (2007-0287), 2007-2011 (Box 485, Folder 3571)
  - University of Pittsburgh: N. Resnick (2004-0212), 2004-2008 (Box 485, Folder 3572)
  - University of Pittsburgh: C. Reynolds III (2004-0334), 2004-2010 (Box 485, Folder 3573-3574)
  - University of Pennsylvania: N. Strumpf (2000-0094), 2000-2007 (Box 485, Folder 3575-3576)
  - University of Pennsylvania: N. Strumpf (2000-0094), 2000-2007 (Box 486, Folder 3577-3579)
  - University of Pennsylvania: J. Johnson (2003-0203), 2003-2008 (Box 486, Folder 3580)
  - University of Pennsylvania: N. Strumpf (2005-0101), 2005-2011 (Box 486, Folder 3581-3582)
  - University of Pennsylvania: N. Strumpf (2005-0101), 2005-2011 (Box 487, Folder 3583-3584)
  - University of Pennsylvania: M. Naylor (2005-0103), 2005-2010 (Box 487, Folder 3585-3586)
  - University of Pennsylvania: J. Johnson (2006-0170), 2006-2011 (Box 487, Folder 3587)
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: J. Busby-Whitehead (2004-0321), 2004-2009 (Box 488, Folder 3588)
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: J. Busby-Whitehead (2008-0145), 2008-2011 (Box 488, Folder 3589)
  - University of Minnesota: J. Wyman (2007-0062), 2007-2013 (Box 488, Folder 3590-3592)
  - University of Minnesota: J. Wyman (2007-0062), 2007-2013 (Box 489, Folder 3593-3595)
  - University of Michigan: J. Halter (2002-0268), 2002-2007 (Box 489, Folder 3596)
  - University of Michigan: J. Halter (2006-0082), 2006-2011 (Box 489, Folder 3597)
  - University of Iowa: K. Buckwalter (2005-0099), 2005-2011 (Box 489, Folder 3598)
  - University of Iowa: K. Buckwalter (2005-0099), 2005-2011 (Box 490, Folder 3599-3603)
  - University of Iowa: K. Buckwalter (2005-0099), 2005-2011 (Box 491, Folder 3604-3605)
  - Center for Health Policy Studies: J. Reuter (80-301), 1980-1985 (Box 491, Folder 3606-3608)
  - Yale University: M. Tinetti (2000-0435), 2000-2005 (Box 491, Folder 3609)
  - Yale University: M. Tinetti (2004-0230), 2004-2008 (Box 492, Folder 3610)
  - Yale University: M. Tinetti (2007-0009), 2007-2011 (Box 492, Folder 3611)
  - Wake Forest University: J. Williamson (2007-0123), 2007-2012 (Box 492, Folder 3612)
  - Visiting Nurse Service of New York: P. Hollander Feldman (2006-0238), 2006-2010 (Box 492, Folder 3613-3614)
  - University of Wisconsin, Madison: S. Asthana (2007-0121), 2007-2012 (Box 492, Folder 3615)
  - University of Washington: I. Abrass (2004-0231), 2004-2009 (Box 493, Folder 3616)
  - University of Washington: I. Abrass (2008-0146), 2008-2011 (Box 493, Folder 3617)
  - University of Utah: M. Supiano (2006-0052), 2006-2009 (Box 493, Folder 3618)
  - University of Utah: G. Pepper (2007-0064), 2007-2012 (Box 493, Folder 3619-3621)
  - University of Utah: G. Pepper (2007-0064), 2007-2012 (Box 494, Folder 3622-3623)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center at San Antonio: D. Espino (2003-0206), 2003-2008 (Box 494, Folder 3624)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center at San Antonio: D. Espino (2006-0171), 2006-2011 (Box 494, Folder 3625-3626)
  - University of Rochester: W. Hall (2003-0211), 2003-2008 (Box 494, Folder 3627)
  - University of Rochester: W. Hall (2007-0008), 2007-2011 (Box 494, Folder 3628)
  - University of Pittsburgh: N. Resnick (2007-0007), 2007-2011 (Box 495, Folder 3629-3630)
  - University of Pittsburgh: C. Reynolds III (2007-0285), 2007-2011 (Box 495, Folder 3631)
  - University of California, San Francisco: M. Wallhagen (2007-0266), 2007-2008 (Box 495, Folder 3632)
  - University of Pennsylvania: S. Douglass (2006-0275), 2006-2007 (Box 495, Folder 3633)
  - University of Utah: M. Keefe (2012-0148) (Box 495, Folder 3634)
  - United Hospital Fund of New York: J. Tallon (98-345), 1997-1998 (Box 495, Folder 3635)
  - United Hospital Fund of New York: J. Tallon (99-633), 1999 (Box 495, Folder 3636)
  - United States Wheelchair Sports Fund: R. Traum (97-129), 1997-1998 (Box 495, Folder 3637)
  - Rheedlen Centers: G. Canada (96-335), 1996-1997 (Box 495, Folder 3638)
  - Rheedlen Centers: G. Canada (98-349), 1998 (Box 495, Folder 3639)
  - University at Albany Foundation: L. Mertz (2005-0128) (Box 495, Folder 3640)
  - Syracuse University: R. Ingles (2001-0149) (Box 495, Folder 3641)
  - Village Center for Care of New York Inc.: J. Hughes (2001-0250), 2001-2005 (Box 495, Folder 3642)
  - Primary Care Development Corporation (PCDC): B. Bieluzcyk (2005-0051) (Box 495, Folder 3643)
  - Peekskill Youth Bureau: V. Swan (2000-0197) (Box 495, Folder 3644)
  - Peekskill Youth Bureau: V. Swan (2000-0488), 2000-2002 (Box 495, Folder 3645)
  - Parkside School: L. Thorne (97-358), 1997-1999 (Box 495, Folder 3646)
  - Parkside School: L. Thorne (95-339), 1995-1997 (Box 495, Folder 3647)
  - Parish Resource Center: J. Stark (98-119), 1997-1998 (Box 495, Folder 3648)
  - Overlook Hospital Foundation: D. Freed (98-137), 1998 (Box 496, Folder 3649)
  - Our Lady of Mercy Medical Center: T. Dharmarajan (98-094), 1998 (Box 496, Folder 3650)
  - Northwest Health Foundation Fund II: J. Woodruff (2011-0024) (Box 496, Folder 3651)
  - Nurses' Educational Funds, Inc.: S. Bowar-Ferres (2013-0206), 2013-2014 (Box 496, Folder 3652)
  - New York Women's Agenda, Inc.: B. Cooper Neufeld (2011-0276) (Box 496, Folder 3653)
  - New York University: T. Fulmer (2007-0138) (Box 496, Folder 3654)
  - New York University: T. Fulmer (2008-0292), 2008-2011 (Box 496, Folder 3655)
  - New York Public Library: P. LeCLerc (97-051), 1995-1999 (Box 496, Folder 3656)
  - New York-Presbyterian Hospital: L. Sardana (2005-0041) (Box 496, Folder 3657)
  - Nutrition Information Center: B. Levin (97-298), 1997 (Box 496, Folder 3658)
  - Cornell Nutrition Information Center: R. Rivlin (98-350), 1998 (Box 496, Folder 3659)
  - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center: Healthy Steps: D. Skinner (96-337), 1996-1997 (Box 496, Folder 3660)
  - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center: Healthy Steps: D. Skinner (97-361), 1997-1999 (Box 496, Folder 3661)
  - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center: Healthy Steps: D. Skinner (98-353), 1998-2000 (Box 496, Folder 3662-3664)
  - Cornell University Medical Center: R. Rivlin (97-343), 1997-1998 (Box 497, Folder 3665)
  - National Senior Volunteer Summit: N. Zionts (98-172), 1998 (Box 497, Folder 3666)
  - National Center for Learning Disabilities: A. Ford (96-190), 1996 (Box 497, Folder 3667)
  - National Association of Social Workers: E. Clark (2005-0048) (Box 497, Folder 3668)
  - National Association of Social Workers: E. Clark (2012-0118) (Box 497, Folder 3669)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center: R. Butler (97-009), 1997 (Box 497, Folder 3670)
  - Mount Sinai School of Medicine: C. Cassel (98-173), 1998 (Box 497, Folder 3671)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center: S. Deprez (2008-0192) (Box 497, Folder 3672)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center: M. Kostegan (2009-0224) (Box 497, Folder 3673)
  - Milwaukee Catholic Home Foundation: M. Weinschrott (2001-0150) (Box 497, Folder 3674)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center: R. Rivlin (97-256), 1997-1998 (Box 497, Folder 3675)
  - Medicare Rights Center: D. Archer (2000-0185), 2000-2003 (Box 497, Folder 3676)
  - Medicare Rights Center: N. Lesavoy (2002-0117) (Box 497, Folder 3677)
  - Medicare Rights Center: R. Hayes (2004-0383) (Box 497, Folder 3678)
  - Medicare Rights Center: R. Hayes (2006-0245) (Box 497, Folder 3679)
  - Madison Square Boys and Girls Club: H. Lowe (96-180), 1996-1997 (Box 497, Folder 3680)
  - Madison Square Boys and Girls Club: A. Bandelato (97-347), 1997 (Box 497, Folder 3681)
  - Marc Lustgarten Foundation for Pancreatic Cancer Research: E. Carnesecca (2005-0072) (Box 497, Folder 3682)
  - Jamaica Center for Arts and Learning: V. LeMelle (98-352), 1998 (Box 497, Folder 3683)
  - International House: D. Cuneo (98-118), 1998 (Box 497, Folder 3684)
  - Independence Care System: R. Surpin (2000-0188) (Box 497, Folder 3685)
  - Hunter College: R. Graziano (2001-0229), 2001-2005 (Box 497, Folder 3686)
  - Hospital for Special Surgery Fund: J. Ahearn (94-374), 1994 (Box 497, Folder 3687)
  - Hospital for Special Surgery Fund: J. Ahearn (95-340), 1995 (Box 497, Folder 3688)
  - Hospital for Special Surgery Fund: J. Ahearn (96-334), 1996 (Box 497, Folder 3689)
  - Hospital for Special Surgery Fund: J. Ahearn (97-359), 1997 (Box 497, Folder 3690)
  - Hospital for Special Surgery Fund: J. Ahearn (98-355), 1998 (Box 497, Folder 3691)
  - Hospital for Special Surgery Fund: J. Ahearn (99-690), 1999 (Box 497, Folder 3692)
  - Hospital for Special Surgery Fund: J. Ahearn (2000-0523) (Box 497, Folder 3693)
  - Hospital for Special Surgery Fund: J. Ahearn (2001-0508), 2001-2002 (Box 497, Folder 3694)
  - Hospital for Special Surgery Fund: J. Ahearn (2003-0055) (Box 497, Folder 3695)
  - Hospital for Special Surgery Fund: D. Sale (2004-0145) (Box 497, Folder 3696)
  - Hospital for Special Surgery Fund: D. Sale (2005-0038) (Box 497, Folder 3697)
  - Hospital for Special Surgery Fund: D. Sale (2006-0057) (Box 497, Folder 3698)
  - Help Line: I. Labiner (2000-0486) (Box 498, Folder 3699)
  - Help Line: I. Labiner (2001-0506) (Box 498, Folder 3700)
  - Helen Keller International: M. Catalano (95-307), 1995-1999 (Box 498, Folder 3701)
  - Gerontological Society of America: C. Schultz (2005-0010) (Box 498, Folder 3702)
  - Gerontological Society of America: J. Appleby (2011-0275) (Box 498, Folder 3703)
  - Gerontological Society of America: J. Appleby (2012-0186) (Box 498, Folder 3704)
  - Grantmakers in Aging: C. Farquhar (2010-0271) (Box 498, Folder 3705)
  - Geriatric Mental Health Foundation: C. deVries (2010-0246) (Box 498, Folder 3706)
  - Fund for the City of New York: M. McCormick (2000-0303), 2000-2001 (Box 498, Folder 3707)
  - Council of Senior Centers and Services of New York City: I. Jellinek (2001-0492), 2001-2003 (Box 498, Folder 3708-3708)
  - Council of Senior Centers and Services of New York: I. Jellinek (2005-0129) (Box 498, Folder 3710)
  - Council of Senior Centers and Services of New York: I. Jellinek (2012-0117) (Box 498, Folder 3711)
  - Community Service Society of New York: A. Molina (99-153), 1999-2000 (Box 499, Folder 3712)
  - Community College of Philadelphia: E. Morgan (2011-0077) (Box 499, Folder 3713)
  - Columbia University Medical Center: R. Sideli (2008-0273) (Box 499, Folder 3714)
  - Children's Oncology Services of Southern Arizona, Inc.: D. Casement (99-521), 1999 (Box 499, Folder 3715)
  - Children's Defense Fund: T. Taylor (97-302), 1997-1998 (Box 499, Folder 3716)
  - Boys Harbor, Inc.: S. Owen (96-077), 1996-2000 (Box 499, Folder 3717)
  - Boys' Club of New York: M. Bunce (95-327), 1992-1995 (Box 499, Folder 3718)
  - Boys' Club of New York: S. Anthony (97-050), 1997-1999 (Box 499, Folder 3719)
  - Boys' Club of New York: M. Bunce (99-634), 1999-2000 (Box 499, Folder 3720)
  - Bowery Residents' Committee, Inc.: J. Sherman (2000-0489) (Box 499, Folder 3721)
  - Bowery Residents' Committee, Inc.: J. Sheehan (2001-0505) (Box 499, Folder 3722)
  - Big Shoulders Fund: J. Hale (2008-0089), 2008-2009 (Box 499, Folder 3723)
  - Association of Baccalaureate Social Work Educators: A. Scott (2007-0267) (Box 499, Folder 3724)
  - Arts Connection: S. Tennen (no grant number), 1996-1997 (Box 499, Folder 3725)
  - American Red Cross in Greater New York: R. Bender (97-132), 1997 (Box 499, Folder 3726)
  - American Red Cross in Greater New York: R. Bender (98-016), 1998 (Box 499, Folder 3727)
  - American Psychiatric Foundation: P. Burke (2012-0298) (Box 499, Folder 3728)
  - American Lung Association of New York: J. Klupt (94-357), 1994 (Box 499, Folder 3729)
  - American Lung Association of New York: G. Caron (97-199), 1997-1998 (Box 499, Folder 3730)
  - American Geriatrics Society Foundation for Health In Aging, Inc.: L. Hiddemen Barondess (2000-0386), 2000-2001 (Box 500, Folder 3731)
  - American Geriatrics Society Foundation for Health In Aging, Inc.: L. Hiddemen Barondess (2001-0376) (Box 500, Folder 3732)
  - American Geriatrics Society Foundation for Health In Aging, Inc.: L. Hiddemen Barondess (2002-0266) (Box 500, Folder 3733)
  - American Geriatrics Society Foundation for Health In Aging, Inc.: L. Hiddemen Barondess (2003-0257) (Box 500, Folder 3734)
  - American Geriatrics Society Foundation for Health In Aging, Inc.: L. Hiddemen Barondess (2004-0207) (Box 500, Folder 3735)
  - American Geriatrics Society Foundation for Health In Aging, Inc.: L. Hiddemen Barondess(2005-0018) (Box 500, Folder 3736)
  - American Geriatrics Society Foundation for Health In Aging, Inc.: L. Hiddemen Barondess(2005-0293) (Box 500, Folder 3737)
  - American Geriatrics Society Foundation for Health In Aging, Inc.: L. Hiddemen Barondess (2006-0234) (Box 500, Folder 3738)
  - American Geriatrics Society Foundation for Health In Aging, Inc.: L. Hiddemen Barondess (2007-0202) (Box 500, Folder 3739)
  - American Geriatrics Society Foundation for Health In Aging, Inc.: L. Hiddemen Barondess (2008-0338) (Box 500, Folder 3740)
  - American Geriatrics Society Foundation for Health In Aging, Inc.: J. Chin Hansen (2010-0247) (Box 500, Folder 3741)
  - American Federation for Aging Research: G. Basche (2002-0001) (Box 500, Folder 3742)
  - American Academy of Nursing: P. Ford-Roegner (2009-0231) (Box 500, Folder 3743)
  - American Academy of Nursing: C. Sullivan (2013-0156), 2013-2014 (Box 500, Folder 3744)
  - Achilles Track Club: L. Winter (96-068), 1996 (Box 500, Folder 3745)
  - Bensonhurst Guidance Center: R. Franchini (99-462), 1999 (Box 500, Folder 3746)
  - Big Apple Circus: P. Cothran (no grant number), 1997 (Box 500, Folder 3747)
  - Brooklyn Public Library: K. Wenderoff (2000-310) (Box 500, Folder 3748)
  - Center for Educational Innovation: L. Monroe (99-154), 1998-1999 (Box 500, Folder 3749)
  - Everybody Wins Foundation, Inc.: J. Goodwin (no grant number), 1997 (Box 500, Folder 3750)
  - Hale House: L. Hale (no grant number), 1998 (Box 500, Folder 3751)
  - Metropolitan Jewish Geriatric Center: N. Gilden (99-100), 1999 (Box 500, Folder 3752)
  - Public Allies: C. Supple (99-482), 1999 (Box 500, Folder 3753)
  - Teaching Matters: N. Cooperman (no grant number), 2001 (Box 500, Folder 3754)
  - Wave Hill: L. DeRespinis (2000-0186) (Box 500, Folder 3755)
  - Harvard Medical School: L. Lipsitz (2002-0267), 2002-2006 (Box 500, Folder 3756)
  - Mount Sinai School of Medicine: R. Leipzig (2002-0272), 2002-2006 (Box 500, Folder 3757)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: D. Reuben (2002-0270), 2002-2006 (Box 500, Folder 3758)
  - Duke University Medical Center: H. Cohen (2002-0269), 2002-2006 (Box 501, Folder 3759-3760)
  - University of Michigan: J. Halter (2002-0268), 2002-2006 (Box 501, Folder 3761)
  - Yale University: M. Tinetti (2000-0435), 2000-2004 (Box 501, Folder 3762)
  - Southeast Center of Excellence: J. Ouslander (2000-0439), 2000-2004 (Box 501, Folder 3763-3764)
  - Southeast Center of Excellence: J. Ouslander (2000-0439), 2000-2004 (Box 502, Folder 3765)
  - University of Rochester: W. Hall (2003-0211), 2003-2007 (Box 502, Folder 3766)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center at San Antonio: D. Espino (2003-0206), 2003-2007 (Box 502, Folder 3767)
  - University of Colorado: A. Kramer (2003-0204), 2003-2007 (Box 502, Folder 3768)
  - Boston Medical Center: R. Silliman (2003-0202), 2003-2007 (Box 502, Folder 3769)
  - University of California, San Francisco: C. Landefeld (2003-0244), 2003-2007 (Box 502, Folder 3770)
  - Baylor College of Medicine: G. Taffet (2003-0205), 2003-2007 (Box 503, Folder 3771-3772)
  - University of Pennsylvania: J. Johnson (2003-0203), 2003-2007 (Box 503, Folder 3773)
  - Southeast Center of Excellence: J. Ouslander (2004-0214), 2004-2007 (Box 503, Folder 3774-3775)
  - University of Washington: I. Abrass (2004-0231), 2004-2007 (Box 503, Folder 3776)
  - Yale University: M. Tinetti (2004-0230), 2004-2007 (Box 504, Folder 3777)
  - University of Hawaii: P. Blanchette (2004-0211), 2004-2007 (Box 504, Folder 3778)
  - Cornell University: M. Reid (2004-0322), 2004-2007 (Box 504, Folder 3779-3780)